jangomail.com 2015-03-15

# JangoMail Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Statement

This privacy statement applies to www.JangoMail.com owned and operated by JangoMail.com LLC. JangoMail has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personally identifiable information provided by those visiting and interacting with the JangoMail public website: [www.jangomail.com](https://www.jangomail.com/) and the JangoMail application (for clients). We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

JangoMail has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability, and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, www.JangoMail.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or practices, please contact us. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Director of Operations at 1-888-465-2646, 8087 Washington Village Drive, Suite 201, Dayton, OH 45458. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

JangoMail complies with the U.S.- EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. JangoMail has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view JangoMail’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

### Your Email Lists and Databases

While using this service, you provide third party email addresses which are owned by you. This data may be imported using an import contacts or database upload feature. JangoMail and its parent company will never sell, rent, share, or otherwise make available your email lists and/or databases to anyone except internal support personnel who may be assisting you in troubleshooting your account, unless it is required to do so in connection with legal process or in accordance with any law, regulation or order of a court or regulatory agency of competent jurisdiction. JangoMail is not in the business of selling data. JangoMail is in the business of providing a web-based mass email service. 

### Website Usage Information

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. JangoMail does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited. This helps us maintain a superior and informative website for you. 

### The Information We Collect

Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, address, and facts about your company size, and similar information. We collect this information so we can fulfill your order, create and administer your account and respond to your customer service requests. We do not request sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card or social security numbers, unless they are signing up for and paying for our services. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies. 

### Access

If you want access to your information to make changes or corrections, please login to your account and update it under “My Account.” If you would like your information deleted, please contact us as described below and we will respond within 30 days. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We may be required to retain some data to meet legal retention requirements. If this is the case, we will let you know in our response to your inquiry. 

### Newsletters

JangoMail sends newsletters and other communications to those who subscribe on our site for the newsletter, free trial, or paid membership. We will use your name and email address to send these communications to you. Newsletters and other JangoMail communications may include tracking technologies that allow us to see when messages have been opened, links clicked, and pages on our own website visited as a response to the emailing. 

### Agents

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

We may also provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

### Security Technology

JangoMail has made a substantial investment in the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center. These investments mean that information about the identity and preferences of individual members is never accessible to anyone outside JangoMail. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. 

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link: <http://www.thawte.com/resources/ssl-information-center/get-started-with-ssl/index.html>. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Widgets

Widgets support functions that require that you disclose certain personally identifiable information, given the user’s choice of participation. This information is collected in many different ways such as: forms, surveys, contests, forums, subscribing or unsubscribing to mailings, and correcting or updating personally identifiable information and are only used for the purpose in which they were collected. Forms which require sensitive information such as financial information (credit card) to process purchases for products or services are SSL encrypted to protect your sensitive information. 

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it. 

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, tracking links, and scripts are used by JangoMail and our affiliates, analytics and service providers, such as email previews, spam scoring tools and support helpdesk. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for authentication and user settings. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. 

### Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [Here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

We use Google AdWords to publish ads on other sites. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on other websites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

### Acquisition or Changes in Ownership of JangoMail

In the event that JangoMail (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, customer information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. If JangoMail is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information. 

### Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

### Links to Other Sites

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by JangoMail. Please be aware that we, JangoMail, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

### Testimonials

If you post a testimonial through tools that we may place on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you would choose to submit. All users have given permission to have their testimonials posted. To request removal of your testimonial, contact us as described below. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your testimonial, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective. 

### Contacting JangoMail about Privacy and JangoMail.com

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact: 

### JangoMail Inquiries

JangoMail  
8087 Washington Village Drive, Suite 201  
Dayton, OH 45458  
Or see the Contact Us page  
Last Updated March 12, 2015
